Hey, what's up, Jaylon? Congrats and
welcome to Indy.
I appreciate you. Yeah.
So, we hear from a lot of O-linemen over
the years that they really have kind of
formed a kinship with Colts O-line coach
Tony Sparano Jr. during the pre-draft
process. Did you have much communication
with the Colts? And if so, did you get
to to interact with coach Sparano much?
For sure. I ain't going to lie, man. I
ain't know uh
coach Sparano, man. He was like one of
like the best guys you know that I
talked to. I could just tell that
everything he did it was just genuine,
you know? And then he loved coach ball
and he loved like the guys that he's
coaching. So, you could tell that
relationships is really important to him
and you know things like that.
James, go ahead.
Again, congrats Jaylon. Um just to
clarify, you so they they have they told
you you're going to stay at guard or or
is that something that's fluid? I don't
know yet. Wherever coach need me to be
is where is where I'm going to be at.
Got you. And then a follow-up to that,
um what excites you about the
opportunity to learn from guys on this
offensive line and obviously one of them
being Quenton Nelson and he's probably a
future Hall of Famer.
For sure, you know what I'm saying?
Like, man, just growing up, you know
what I'm saying? Watching the O-line,
you know what the trenches are like,
just knowing what it look like and
things like that and really just seeing
a guy like that and
the way he play the game, like he do it
all the right way. So, like being able
to be in the room with a guy like that
is going to be real cool to learn from,
you know what I'm saying? So,
Abby.
Uh Jaylon, congratulations. You are the
third um SEC player taken by the Colts
in this draft.
Chris Ballard three for three from the
SEC. What about that level of play do
you think will translate best into the
league?
I just want to it overly speaks for
itself, you know? If that if that makes
sense, you know, like the SEC is damn
near like the closest thing to the
National Football League. So, I
most definitely understand why coach do
is doing is doing what he's doing.
Joel.
What uh what do you think clicked when
you made it to Kentucky? You were you
were at Florida for a couple years then
as soon as you got to Kentucky you kind
of hit the ground running in the
starting lineup.
Um man, honestly just really having some
really good coaches at Florida and them
putting like the right battery in my
back, you know, to have like the right
mindset if I was to be there or not, you
know? So, but me going to Kentucky and
having some more good coaches but
different in a way if that makes sense,
you know? It's just it it it made that
process a really easy, you feel me?
James, go ahead. All right, Jaylon, from
a human perspective, uh probably one of
the biggest days of your life. So, can
you just give us the behind-the-scenes,
like, you know, where were you when you
got the call and just the emotions of
getting to this stage?
Man, honestly, man, I'm just I'm back
home in Atlanta, you know, with the fam.
Ain't nothing too big, ain't nothing too
crazy, you know? Just everybody who's
really important to me. So,
just like really just simple like that,
you know? But, man, you know,
it's like
I'm playing ball since 7 years old, you
know what I'm saying? It's like the day
is finally here, you know? But, it's not
time to stop, it's time to, you know,
just going to keep going. So, I'm most
definitely appreciative.
What did you say your name was, RJ?
Yeah, so Abby mentioned you're you're
from the SEC and you have been the other
guys they've drafted on the defensive
side of the ball. Do you have any
recollection of playing against Georgia
linebacker C.J. Allen and LSU safety uh
A.J. Halsey? Um I didn't go against the
safety but C.J. dog uh as dog, that's
it.